<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Beatles Anthology Vol. 1</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Behind That Locked Door: Beatles Rarities!</string>
    <string name="article_text">In a vault deep inside Abbey Road Studios in London - protected by an unmarked,triple-locked,police alarmed door - are something like 400 hours of unreleased beatle recordings,starting from june 2,1962 and ending with the very last tracks recorded for the let it be album.the best of the best were released by apple records in the form of 3-volume Anthology series.
         For more information,see the Beatles Time Capsule at www.rockument.com.

    \n\n
    This volume starts with the first new Beatle song,"Free as a Bird"(based on john lennon demo,found only on<i>The Lost Lennon Tapes Vol.28</i>

    \n\n
    <b>Highlights include</b>

    \n\n
    <b><i>Cry for a shadow</i></b> - Many a beatle fanatic started down the outtake road,like i did, with a first Listen to this song.Originally titles "Beatle Bop" and recorded in a single session that yielded four songs(The other three featured Tony Sheridan with the Beatles as backing band)."Cry for a shadow" is an instrumental written by lennon and Harrison which makes it unique to this day .john lennon plays rhythm guitar


    \n\n
    <b><i>Leave my kitten alone</i></b>is a 1959  hit, written by Little Willie John, Titus Turner and James McDougal, first recorded by Little Willie John. An early version by the Beatles was released in 1994 on Anthology 1. The song follows a 24-bar blues format.The original version of the song, by Little Willie John, on King Records, reached No. 13 on the Billboard chart and No. 60 on the pop chart on its first release in 1959. A second release again reached No. 60, after cover version by Johnny Preston reached No.

    \n\n
    <b><i>One after 909</i></b> is a song by the English rock band the Beatles from their 1970 album Let It Be. It was written by John Lennon, with input from Paul McCartney and was credited to their joint partnership. The album version is the live performance from the rooftop concert which took place on 30 January 1969. This performance is also included in the Let It Be film. The song was written no later than spring 1960 and perhaps as early as 1957, and is one of the first Lennon–McCartney compositions. "One After 909" is perhaps more reminiscent of early American rock.

    </string>
</resources>